Wilna Hervey and Nan Mason
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Wilna Hervey and Nan Mason papers
1883-1985
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Hervey, Wilna
4.9 linear feet
The papers of artist and silent film actress Wilna Hervey and her lifelong companion painter Nan Mason date from 1883 through 1985 and measure 4.9 linear feet. The collection is comprised mostly of letters to Hervey and Mason from friends, colleagues, and Mason's father, Dan Mason, also a silent film actor. Also found are personal photographs and snapshots, Hervey's handwritten memoirs, as well as twelve folders of Dan Mason's papers.
Provenance
The Wilna Hervey and Nan Mason papers were donated to the Archives of American Art by Daniel Gelfand, a friend of Wilna Hervey and Nan Mason, in 2008.
Restrictions on Access
Use of the original papers requires an appointment.
Biographical Note
Wilna Hervey was born in 1894 and grew up in Far Rockaway, New York. She met Nan Mason (1896-1982), daughter of silent film actor Dan Mason, while on production of The Toonerville Trolley silent film comedies in 1920. They were lifelong companions until Hervey's death in 1979.
As a young woman in the late 1910s, Hervey took art lessons at the Art Students League in New York City, Winold Reiss' studio at 4 Christopher Street, New York City, and during the summer of 1918 in Woodstock, New York. In 1919, she joined the Betzwood Studios in Audubon, Pennsylvania to play the role of "The Powerful Katrinka" in The Toonerville Trolley, a series of silent films based on Fontaine Fox's comic strip. Co-star Dan Mason, who played the Skipper, took Hervey under his wing, and Hervey lived with the Masons while filming the series. After The Toonerville Trolley series ended in 1921, Dan and Nan Mason traveled to Hollywood to start a new company, and Wilna followed shortly after, taking the train across the country in early 1922. The new endeavor, Plum Street Comedies, began at the Paul Gerson Pictures Corporation in San Francisco and was based on The Toonerville Trolley series; the film crew included the young Frank Capra. The Plum Street Comedies were in production for only one year, 1922-1923.
Around 1919-1920, Hervey's father bought Wilna a small studio in Bearsville, New York. From 1922-1929 Hervey and Nan Mason split their time between painting and farming in Woodstock, New York, and pursuing acting while living with Dan Mason in California. In 1926-1927, the women traveled to Europe and North Africa together to see museums, art, and architecture.
After the death of Dan Mason in 1929, Hervey and Nan Mason made Bearsville their permanent home. Beginning in the late 1950s, Hervey and Mason began spending winters in Anna Maria, Florida and summers in New York. Hervey and Mason achieved success as artists in the 1960s - Hervey as an enamel painter, and Mason as a painter and photographer.
Wilna Hervey passed away in 1979, and Nan Mason died in 1982.
Sources consulted include "The Biggest Girl" by Joseph P. Eckhardt (http://faculty.mc3.edu/jeckhard/biggestgirlarticle/thebiggestgirl.html).
Scope and Content Note
The papers of artist and silent film actress Wilna Hervey and her lifelong companion painter Nan Mason date from 1883 through 1985 and measure 4.9 linear feet. The collection is comprised mostly of letters to Hervey and Mason from friends, colleagues, and Mason's father, Dan Mason, also a silent film actor. Also found are personal photographs and snapshots, Hervey's handwritten memoirs, as well as twelve folders of Dan Mason's papers.
Biographical materials include a personal narrative, notes on family history, newspaper clippings related to family, legal and financial records, and Wilna Hervey's notes on artwork.
Hervey and Mason were friends with many artists and their correspondence includes letters from artists such as Albert Heckman, Georgina Klitgaard, Manuel Komroff, Leon Kroll, Doris Lee, Fred Dana Marsh, Henry Lee McFee, William Pachner, Caroline and Paul Rohland, Andrée Ruellan, Eugene Speicher, and Dorothy Varian. There are very few letters written by Hervey or Mason, and the correspondence is mostly personal in nature. There are over 250 letters from Elsie Speicher, wife of portrait artist Eugene Speicher. Correspondence to Dan Mason has been separated and is filed in a separate series.
Wilna Hervey wrote a a number of handwritten memoirs of her days in the The Toonerville Trolley film series. She had hopes of publishing these one day and worked with writer Karin Whiteley on the project. Although her memoirs were never published, Hervey and Whiteley wrote and compiled materials for the book. Included in the Memoir Book Production series are handwritten memoirs by Hervey chronicling her years prior to and during the 1920s (many of the handwritten memoirs have been typed by Karin Whiteley). It also includes research materials, such as two typed synopses of The Toonerville Trolley scripts from Fontaine Fox's files, newspaper clippings, and playbills, seemingly intended to provide background and verification of the memoirs.
This collection also includes a few pieces of artwork; three small watercolor sketches by an unidentified artist, and a print by Edward Chavez.
Photographs are mostly snapshots of friends and family, life in Woodstock, New York and Anna Maria, Florida. Negatives originally housed in an un-postmarked envelope with a return address labeled "Betzwood Film Co.," appear to be from the filming of The Toonerville Trolley. In several of the negatives Wilna Hervey is dressed as The Powerful Katrinka, and in one negative Dan Mason is The Skipper.
The personal files of Dan Mason include letters from Hervey and Nan Mason, the bulk from their trip to Europe and North Africa in 1926-1927. This series also includes Dan Mason's own handwritten and typed memoirs, newspaper clippings, and financial records.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into six series:
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1916-1960 (Box 1; 5 folders)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1890-1985 (Box 1-10, OV 13; 3.8 linear feet)
Series 3: Memoir Book Production, 1883-1959 (Box 11, OV 13; 0.4 linear feet)
Series 4: Artwork, 1961, undated (Box 11, OV 13; 2 folders)
Series 5: Photographs, circa 1915 - 1982 (Box 12; 5 folders)
Series 6: Personal Files of Dan Mason, 1919-1928 (Box 12; 0.4 linear feet)
Names and Subject Terms
This collection is indexed in the online catalog of the Archives of American Art under the following terms:
Subjects:
Mason, Dan, 1853-1929; Mason, Nan, 1896-1982
Subjects-Topical:
Motion picture actors and actresses; Women painters -- New York (State)
Types of Materials:
Photographs
Names:
Heckman, Albert; Klitgaard, Georgina, 1889-1977; Komroff, Manuel, 1890-; Kroll, Leon, 1884-1974; Lee, Doris, 1905-1983; Marsh, Fred Dana, 1872-1961; Mason, Dan, 1853-1929; Mason, Nan, 1896-1982; McFee, Henry Lee, 1886-1953; Pachner, William, 1915-; Rohland, Paul,$d1884-1953; Ruellan, Andrée, 1905-; Speicher, Elsie, d. 1959; Speicher, Eugene E. (Eugene Edward), 1883-1962; Rohland, Caroline; Varian, Dorothy, 1895-1987
Series Descriptions/Container Listing
- Biographical Material, 1916-1960, Series 1:; (Box 1; 5 folders)
  This series includes a personal narrative, notes on family history, newspaper clippings related to family, legal and financial records, and Wilna Hervey's notes on artwork.
  - Personal Narrative, 1916 (Folder 1)
  - Notes on Family, after 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Legal and Financial Records, circa 1927-1960 (Folder 3)
  - Notes on Artwork, 1960 (Folder 4)
  - Clippings and Printed Material, circa 1931-1945 (Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1890-1985, Series 2:; (Box 1-10, OV 13; 3.8 linear feet)
  Correspondence is mostly personal letters and covers subjects such as personal matters, updates on the lives of Woodstock residents, and the careers of artist friends. Early correspondence highlights Wilna Hervey's film career and travels. Other than the letters written by Nan Mason to Wilna Hervey, there are very few letters in this series written by either Hervey or Mason.
  Notable correspondents include artists and friends Albert Heckman, Georgina Klitgaard, Manuel Komroff, Leon Kroll, Doris Lee, Fred Dana Marsh, Henry Lee McFee, William Pachner, Caroline and Paul Rohland, Andrée Ruellan, Eugene Speicher, and Dorothy Varian. There are over 250 letters from Elsie Speicher, wife of portrait artist Eugene Speicher. The bulk of Elsie Speicher's correspondence is from the months of November - March; between April to October each year the Speichers were usually in Woodstock with Hervey and Mason. Speicher occasionally sends correspondence from friends in common, notably Louise Lindin, Daphne Mattson, Caroline Rohland, Jean Rosen, and Andrée Ruellan.
  Early correspondence from Karin Whiteley concerns a project to publish Hervey's memoirs (which were never published). Whiteley's correspondence also includes numerous enclosed newspaper clippings regarding Dan Mason's acting career. Additional correspondence from Karin Whiteley regarding the memoirs is located in Series 3: Memoir Book Production, 1883-1959. Other items of interest in this series includes a letter from Robert Pollack (1918) that includes a Smileage Book (movie coupons from the Military Entertainment Service), a New York City subway ticket, and caricatures drawn by Wilna Hervey, illustrated letters by cartoonist John Striebel, and occasional snapshots of artists and friends. Correspondence to Dan Mason from Hervey and Nan Mason has been separated and is filed with the other personal files of Dan Mason in Series 6, 1919-1928.
  This series also includes correspondence that was neither written by Hervey or Mason, nor sent to them. It may be that the letters were sent to Hervey and Mason as enclosures in other correspondence. Such correspondence is arranged at the end of this series as Miscellaneous Collected Correspondence.
  See Index for list of correspondents.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by the correspondent's last name and then chronologically within folders; undated letters are located at the end of the folder. Correspondents with fewer than five letters are filed by last name in folders labeled alphabetically. Letters from unidentified correspondents are filed at the end of the series.
  Index of selected correspondents from Series 2: Correspondence
  Adams, Kenneth M.: 1955
  Antenucci, Margaret: 1961
  Arndt, Paul Wesley: 1976
  Baumann, Mag and George: 1964, 1970
  Bellows, Emma: 1948-1958
  Bentley, John W. (Jack): 1922, 1931
  Bettels, Kathryn: 1926
  Blanch, Lucile and Arnold: 1931, 1955
  Booth, Jean Bellows: 1945-1978
  Cannon, Eleanor Rixson: 1950-1954
  Capra, Frank: 1935, 1973
  Carlson, Margaret: 1958
  Cator, Bruce: 1948-1959
  Cator, Eleanor: circa 1924
  Cator, Thomas Vincent: 1928-1929
  Chavez, Edward and Jenne: 1950-1952
  Clark, Susan: 1960-1966
  Clement, Jean: 1931, undated
  Currie, Bruce: 1946, circa 1951-1952
  De La Vergne, Gladys Hurlbut: 1959, undated
  Eddy, Ruth: 1934-1959
  Ganso, Emil and Nina: 1933
  Gonzales, Betty (Mrs. Boyer Gonzales): 1959
  Gonzales, Nell (Mrs. Boyer Gonzales): 1936
  Harris, Alexandrina (Allie): 1926, 1931, 1959
  Harrison, Jenny (Mrs. Birge Harrison): 1941, 1945
  Heckman, Albert and Florence: 1949-1964
  Hervey, Anna: 1908-1922
  Hervey, W.R.: 1913-1925
  Hervey, Wilna: circa 1919-1961
  Hitzig, William M.: 1940-1972
  Holt, Percy W.: 1923-1930, 1953
  Karoly: 1939
  Kesselring, Joe and Charlotte: 1949-1952
  Klitgaard, Georgina: 1933, 1974, undated
  Komroff, Odette and Manuel: 1945-1978
  Kroll, Leon: 1939, 1963
  Laufman, Beatrice (Mrs. Sidney Laufman): 1970
  Lee, Doris: 1950-1953
  Lindin, Louise (Mrs. Carl Lindin): 1936-1968
  Loederer, Richard: 1923-1924
  Magafan, Ethel: 1957
  Marsh, Fred Dana: 1948-1952
  Mason, Dan: 1921-1929
  Mason, Nan: 1919-1921
  Mattson, Henry and Daphne: 1931-1959
  McFee, Aileen (Mrs. Henry Lee McFee): circa 1928-1936
  McFee, Henry Lee: 1931-1936
  Mearns, Hughes and Fagley: 1942, circa 1952-1960
  More, Edna (Mrs. Hermon More): 1930-1943
  Pachner, Lorraine "Zombie" (Mrs. William Pachner): 1949-1978
  Pachner, William: circa 1950-1975
  Petersham, Maud and Miska: circa 1930s-1959
  Pollock, Muriel "Mollie" (Donaldson): circa 1916-1959
  Rheinish, Arthur: 1920-1921
  Rohland, Caroline Speare: 1926-1960
  Rohland, Paul: circa 1931, 1935
  Rosen, Jean (Mrs. Charles Rosen): 1936-circa 1961
  Rosen, M. (Mrs. Charles Rosen): 1924-1927
  Rosen, Polly: before 1959
  Ruellan, Andrée (Mrs. John Taylor): 1943-1977
  Search, Frederick Preston: 1933
  Shore, Henrietta: 1933
  Smith, Georgine Wetherell: 1951-1953
  Speicher, Charles: 1931-1945
  Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher): 1926-1959
  Speicher, Eugene: 1935-1961
  Striebel, Fritzi (Mrs. John H. Striebel): 1946-1978
  Striebel, John H.: 1961
  Summers, D.: 1952-1961
  Summers, Pauline "Paul": 1952-1961
  Varian, Dorothy: 1954-1977
  Webster, Florence: 1954, 1978
  Weston, Brett: 1958
  Weston, Edward: 1935, 1951
  Whiteley, Karin: 1945-1981
  - A-B, 1922-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Booth, Jean Bellows, 1945-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - C, 1928-1975, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - Cannon, Eleanor Rixson, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cator, Bruce, 1948-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cator, Eleanor, circa 1924 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Clark, Susan, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - D-F, 1939-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Eddy, Ruth, 1934-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - G, 1933-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - H, 1926-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Heckman, Albert and Florence, 1949-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hervey, Anna, 1908-1922, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
  - Hervey, W.R., 1913-1925 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hervey, Wilna, circa 1919-1961, (includes draft letters) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hitzig, William M., 1940-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Holt, Percy W., 1923-1930, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - I-K, 1921-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Komroff, Odette and Manuel, 1945-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - L, 1923-1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lindin, Louise (Mrs. Carl Lindin), 1936-1968, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - M, circa 1924-circa 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Marsh, Fred Dana, 1948-1952, (includes pen sketches) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Mason, Dan, 1921, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mason, Dan, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mason, Dan, 1925, (includes newspaper clippings; oversized material housed in OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mason, Dan, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mason, Dan, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mason, Dan, 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Mason, Nan, 1919-1921, (2 folders; includes pen sketches) (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Mattson, Henry and Daphne, 1931-1959, (includes color pencil drawing) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - McFee, Aileen (Mrs. Henry Lee McFee), circa 1928-1936 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mearns, Hughes and Fagley, 1942, circa 1952-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - N-P, 1918-1934 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Pachner, Lorraine "Zombie" (Mrs. William Pachner), 1949-1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Pachner, William, circa 1950-1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Petersham, Maud and Miska, circa 1930s-1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pollock, Muriel "Mollie" (Donaldson), circa 1916-1959, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - R, 1920-before 1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Rheinish, Arthur, 1920-1921 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Rohland, Caroline Speare, 1926-1933, (includes pencil sketch) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Rohland, Caroline Speare, 1934-1940, (includes two negatives) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rohland, Caroline Speare, 1942-1951, (includes two photographs of Paul Rohland) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rohland, Caroline Speare, 1952-1960, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rosen, Jean (Mrs. Charles Rosen), 1936-circa 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ruellan, Andrée (Mrs. John Taylor), 1943-1977, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - S, 1922-1970, (2 folders; includes illustrated letter by John Streibel) (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Smith, Georgine Wetherell, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1926-1935 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1936 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1941 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1942, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1943, (4 folders) (Box 7, Folder 3-6)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1944, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 7-9)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1945, (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1946 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1949 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1950 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1951 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1952 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), 1955-1959 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Speicher, Elsie (Mrs. Eugene Speicher), circa 1926-1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Speicher, Eugene, 1935-1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Striebel, Fritzi (Mrs. John Striebel), 1946-1978, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - T-Z, 1924-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Varian, Dorothy, 1954-1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Whiteley, Karin, 1945-1981, (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Identified by First Name, A-J, circa 1923-1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Identified by First Name, M-Z, circa 1916-1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Sender, circa 1926-1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Collected Correspondence, 1890-1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Memoir Book Production, 1883-1959, Series 3:; (Box 11, OV 13; 0.4 linear feet)
  Wilna Hervey intended to publish memoirs of her days involved in The Toonerville Trolley films. Included in this series are handwritten memoirs chronicling her years prior to and during the 1920s (many of the handwritten memoirs have been typed by Karin Whiteley and are also located in this series).
  This series also includes research materials such as typed synopses of two Toonerville Trolley scripts copied from the files of Fontaine Fox, correspondence with sketches from Fontaine Fox to Dan Mason, "The Little Folks Paper," published in 1891, playbills, writings and notes from unidentified sources, an indenture of deed, a deed of trust by Thomas Vincent Cator, newspaper clippings and advertisements. Within the series is one oversized drawing from an unidentified artist, undated.
  The majority of the correspondence is to Hervey from Karin Whiteley (additional correspondence from Karin Whiteley regarding the memoir is located in Series 2: Correspondence, 1890-1985). Correspondence also includes Hervey's contract with The Paul Gerson Pictures Corporation dated 1922, and typed and handwritten writings by Dan Mason.
  Items are arranged in original order.
  - Memoir Writings by Wilna Hervey, circa 1956-1957, (3 folders) (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Research Materials, 1883-circa 1976, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1959, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Artwork by Unidentified Artist, undated, (Oversized material housed in OV 13) (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Artwork, 1961, undated, Series 4:; (Box 11, OV 13; 2 folders)
  This series includes three small watercolor sketches by unidentified artist, and a print by Edward Chavez.
  - Watercolor sketches by unknown artist, undated, (3 sketches) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Print by Edward Chavez, 1961, (Oversized, housed in OV 13) (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Photographs, circa 1915-1982, Series 5:; (Box 12; 5 folders)
  Photographs in this series are mostly snapshots of friends and family, life in Woodstock, New York and Anna Maria, Florida. Black and white snapshots contain photos of unidentified costumed people at an outdoor party, Wilna Hervey gardening, Elsie and Eugene Speicher, Charles Rosen, Nan Mason and Wilna Hervey in Italy in 1926, and of a home in a forested setting. Color snapshots are of gardens, beach scenes, and unidentified women. Negatives were originally found in an un-postmarked envelope with a return address labeled "Betzwood Film Co." and include six negatives of people on a boat, including Wilna Hervey and Dan Mason. Twenty-one negatives appear to be from a camera shoot for the Toonerville Trolley films. In several of the negatives Wilna Hervey is dressed as The Powerful Katrinka, and in one negative Dan Mason is The Skipper.
  - Black and White Snapshots, circa 1915 - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Color Snapshots, circa 1950-1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Negatives, circa 1920-1921, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
  - Negatives from Georgina Klitgaard, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Personal Files of Dan Mason, 1919-1928, Series 6:; (Box 12; 0.4 linear feet)
  The personal files of Dan Mason include correspondence to Mason, Mason's own handwritten and typed memoirs, newspaper clippings, and financial records mostly related to the death of his wife, Millicent Mason in 1919. The bulk of the correspondence is written by Wilna Hervey and Nan Mason, and chronicles their trip to Europe and North Africa in 1926-1927, as well as their close relationship with Dan Mason. Correspondence also includes a few family snapshots.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically and then chronologically. Memoirs, financial records, and newspaper clippings are arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence from Nan Mason, 1926, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence from Nan Mason, 1927 January (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from Nan Mason, 1927 February-1928 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from Wilna Hervey, 1926-1927 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1922-1927 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Envelopes, 1924-1928 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Memoirs, circa 1920s, (3 folders) (Box 12, Folder 13-15)
  - Financial Records, 1919-1927 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1924-1926 (Box 12, Folder 17)